Come in.
进来。
And?
然后呢?
Nothing?
没有什么?
She won't eat.
她不吃东西。
We'll try again at supper.
晚饭时我们再试一次。
I think they're watching me.
我觉得他们在监视我。
- Who?
- Her soldiers.
——谁?
-她的士兵。
Of course they are. That's their job.
当然了。那是他们的工作。
What have I told you, Martha?
我怎么跟你说的，玛莎？
The greater the risk,
the greater the reward.
风险越大，
回报就越大。
Go on. They'll be missing you
in the kitchen.
继续。他们会想你的
在厨房里。
Varys: The northern armies?
瓦里斯：北境军队？
Jon: Just crossed the trident.
乔恩：刚刚跨过三叉戟。
They'll be at the walls
of king's landing in two days.
他们会在城墙边
两天后君临
How is she?
她怎么样了？
She hasn't seen anyone
since we returned.
她谁也没见过
自从我们回来。
Hasn't left her chambers,
hasn't accepted any food.
没有离开她的房间，
没有接受任何食物。
She shouldn't be alone.
她不应该一个人。
You're worried for her.
I admire your empathy.
你在为她担心。
我钦佩你的同情心。
Aren't you worried for her?
你不担心她吗？
I'm worried for all of us.
我为我们所有人担心。
They say every time
a Targaryen is born,
他们说每一次
坦格利安家族诞生
the gods toss a coin
and the world holds its breath.
诸神掷硬币
整个世界都屏住呼吸。
We're not much for riddles
where I'm from.
我们不太喜欢猜谜
我来自哪里？
We both know what she's about to do.
我们都知道她要做什么。
That's her decision to make.
She is our queen.
这是她自己的决定。
她是我们的女王。
Men decide where power resides,
whether or not they know it.
权力归属于人，
不管他们是否知道。
What do you want?
你想要什么？
All I've ever wanted.
我想要的一切。
The right ruler on the iron throne.
铁王座上的正确统治者。
I still don't know
how her coin has landed.
我还是不知道
她的硬币是如何落地的。
But I'm quite certain about yours.
但我很确定你的。
I don't want it.
我不想要。
Ineverhave.
Ineverhave。
I have known more kings and queens
than any man living.
我认识了更多的国王和王后
比任何活着的人。
I've heard what they say to crowds,
and seen what they do in the shadows.
我听过他们对人群说的话，
看到他们在暗处的所作所为。
I have furthered their designs,
however horrible.
我助长了他们的阴谋，
然而可怕的。
But what I tell you now is true:
但我现在告诉你们的是真的。
You will rule wisely and well,
while she...
你会统治得很好，
而她……
She...
她……
Is my queen.
是我的女王。
Your grace?
你的恩典吗?
There's something you need to know.
有些事你得知道。
Someone has betrayed me.
有人背叛了我。
Yes.
是。
Jon snow.
琼恩雪诺。
Varys.
不同。
He knows the truth about Jon.
他知道乔恩的真相。
He does.
他所做的。
Because you told him.
因为你告诉他了。
You learned from sansa.
你跟珊莎学的。
And she learned from Jon,
她从乔恩那里学到了，
though I begged him not to tell her.
虽然我求他不要告诉她。
As I said...
正如我所说的……
He betrayed me.
他背叛了我。
I'm glad sansa told me.
我很高兴珊莎告诉了我。
I am your hand.
我是你的手。
I need to be aware
of any threats you're facing.
我需要意识到
你所面临的威胁。
And varys?
和不同?
Your master of whisperers
needs to be aware too.
你的耳语大师
也需要注意。
You spoke to him first.
你先跟他说的。
Without coming to me.
不要来找我。
Without asking my permission.
没有征得我的同意。
It was a mistake.
这是个错误。
Why do you think sansa told you?
不然珊莎为什么告诉你？
- What do you think she hoped to gain?
- She trusts me.
-你认为她希望得到什么？
-她信任我
Yes, she trusts you.
是的，她信任你。
She trusted you to spread secrets
她信任你去传播秘密
that could destroy your own queen.
那会毁了你的王后。
And you did not let her down.
你也没有让她失望。
If I have failed you, my queen,
forgive me.
如果我辜负了你，我的女王，
原谅我。
Our intentions were good.
我们的初衷是好的。
We wanted what you want.
A better world, all of us.
我们想要你想要的。
一个更美好的世界，我们所有人。
Varys as much as anyone.
瓦里斯和其他人一样。
But it doesn't matter now.
但现在已经不重要了。
It doesn't matter now.
现在不重要了。
It was me.
是我。
I hope I deserve this.
希望这是我应得的。
Truly, I do.
真的，我知道。
I hope I'm wrong.
我希望我错了。
Goodbye, old friend.
再见，老朋友。
Lord varys.
主有所不同。
I, Daenerys of house Targaryen,
first of my name,
我，坦格利安家族的丹妮莉丝，
首先是我的名字，
breaker of chains
and mother of dragons...
断链器
龙之母……
Sentence you to die.
判你死刑。
Dracarys.
Dracarys。
This was all she brought with her
when we crossed the narrow sea.
这是她带来的所有东西
当我们穿过狭窄的海面。
Her only possession.
她唯一的财产。
It's all right, torgo nudho.
没关系，再见，再见。
Let me speak with him.
让我和他谈谈。
What did I say
would happen if you told your sister?
我说什么来着？
如果你告诉你妹妹会怎么样？
I don't want it,
and that's what I told him.
我不想要，
我就是这么告诉他的
She betrayed your trust.
她辜负了你的信任。
She killed varys as much as I did.
她和我一样杀了瓦里斯。
This was a victory for her.
这是她的胜利。
Now she knows what happens
when people hear the truth about you.
现在她知道会发生什么了
当人们听到关于你的真相。
Far more people in Westeros
love you than love me.
维斯特洛的人口要多得多
爱你胜过爱我。
I don't have love here.
我这里没有爱。
I only have fear.
我只有恐惧。
I love you.
我爱你。
And you will always be my queen.
你永远是我的女王。
Is that all I am to you?
这就是我对你的意义吗？
Your queen?
你的女王吗?
All right, then.
那好吧。
Let it be fear.
让它成为恐惧吧。
Tyrion: The people who live there,
they're not your enemies.
提利昂：住在那里的人，
他们不是你的敌人。
They're innocents, like the ones
you liberated in meereen.
他们是无辜的，就像那些
你在弥林解放了。
Daenerys: In meereen,
the slaves turned on the masters
丹妮莉丝：在会议上，
奴隶们背叛了主人
and liberated the city themselves
the moment I arrived.
解放了这座城市
在我到达的那一刻。
Tyrion: They're afraid.
提利昂：他们害怕。
Anyone who resists Cersei
will see his family butchered.
任何反抗瑟曦的人
会看到他的家人被屠杀。
You can't expect them to be heroes.
你不能指望他们成为英雄。
- They're hostages.
- They are.
-他们是人质。
-是的。
In a tyrant's grip.
Whose fault is that? Mine?
在暴君的控制之下。
这是谁的错？我的吗?
What does it matter whose fault it is?
这是谁的错有什么关系？
Thousands of children will die
if the city burns.
成千上万的儿童将会死亡
如果城市燃烧。
Your sister knows how to use
her enemies' weaknesses against them.
你妹妹知道怎么用
她的敌人对他们的弱点。
That's what she thinks our mercy is:
这就是她认为我们的仁慈
Weakness.
的弱点。
- I beg you, my queen...
- But she's wrong.
-我求求你，我的女王…
-但她错了。
Mercy is our strength.
仁慈是我们的力量。
Our mercy towards future generations
我们对后代的怜悯
who will never again
be held hostage by a tyrant.
再也不会
被暴君挟持。
Ready the unsullied.
准备好无垢者。
Tonight you sail for king's landing
to join the northern armies.
今晚你坐船去君临
加入北方军队。
Cersei's followers will abandon her
if they know the war is lost.
瑟曦的追随者会抛弃她
如果他们知道战争失败了。
Give them that chance.
给他们这个机会。
If the city surrenders, they will
ring the bells and raise the gates.
如果城市投降，他们会的
敲响钟声，打开大门。
Please, if you hear them ringing
the bells, call off the attack.
请，如果你听到铃声
钟声响起，取消进攻。
Daenerys: Wait for me
outside the city.
丹妮莉丝：等等我
在城外。
You'll know when it's time.
到时候你就知道了。
Daenerys: Your brother was stopped
trying to get past our lines.
丹妮莉丝：你哥哥被拦住了
试图越过我们的防线。
It seems he hasn't abandoned
your sister after all.
看来他并没有放弃
毕竟是你妹妹。
The next time you fail me...
下次你再让我失望…
Will be the last time you fail me.
这是你最后一次让我失望。
Guard 1: Let them pass.
警卫1：让他们过去。
Guard 2: Through the gate.
警卫2：穿过大门。
Guard 3: Get going.
卫兵3：快走。
Davos: The rearguard
should be here by daybreak.
戴佛斯：后卫
黎明前应该能到。
Tyrion: She wants to attack now.
提利昂：她现在就想进攻。
Daybreak at the earliest.
最早要天亮。
Soldier 1: Careful with that.
Soldier 2: My lord.
士兵1：小心点。
士兵2：大人。
Tyrion: Davos.
泰瑞欧:达沃斯。
I need to ask you a favor.
我想请你帮个忙。
You're the greatest smuggler alive,
aren't you?
你是世界上最伟大的走私者
不是吗?
I'm not gonna like this favor, am I?
我不会喜欢这个忙的，对吧？
Soldier 1: He's always better
when he's got some food in him.
士兵1：他总是比我强
等他吃饱了再说。
Soldier 2: Problem is
when he's got drink in him.
士兵2：问题是
当他喝多了的时候。
- See what he did the other week?
- Soldier 1: Aye. Fighting as well.
-看看他前几周做了什么？
-士兵1：是的。还有打架。
Ay up. Where you going?
是的。你要去哪里？
I'm Arya stark.
我是艾莉亚·史塔克。
I'm going to kill queen Cersei.
我要去杀瑟曦太后。
Think about it.
She kills Cersei, the war's over.
想想看。
她杀了瑟曦，战争就结束了。
There won't be a siege.
You might not even die tomorrow.
不会有围城。
你也许明天就不会死。
I need to go talk to my captain.
我要去和我的队长谈谈。
Go ahead, talk to him.
去吧，跟他谈谈。
Soldier 1: Where's he going?
士兵1：他要去哪里？
I drink to eat the skull keeper.
我喝酒是为了吃骷髅守护者。
I want to eat the skull keeper.
我想吃掉骷髅守护者。
I want to see the...
我想看看……
Unsullied soldier:
We speak the common tongue.
清白的士兵:
我们说共同的语言。
Ah. Good.
啊。好。
I want to be alone with the prisoner.
我想单独和犯人待在一起。
Get some rest.
Tomorrow will be a long day.
休息一下。
明天将是漫长的一天。
Unsullied soldier:
We have orders to guard the prisoner.
清白的士兵:
我们奉命看守囚犯。
Ordered by whom? The queen herself?
谁订的？女王本人？
Unsullied soldier: No.
无垢战士：不。
Well, in that case,
as hand of the queen,
这样的话，
作为女王之手，
I outrank whomever gave your order.
我的级别比给你下命令的人高。
Probably by quite a lot.
可能相差很多。
How did they find you?
他们怎么找到你的？
Did you consider taking it off?
你考虑过把它摘下来吗？
Cersei once called me
"the stupidest Lannister."
瑟曦曾打电话给我
“最愚蠢的兰尼斯特。”
You're going back to her,
to die with her.
你要回到她身边
和她一起死。
You've underestimated her before.
你以前低估了她。
She's going to die.
她要死了。
Unless you can convince her
to change her course of action.
除非你能说服她
改变她的行动方针。
Difficult to do from here.
从这里很难做到。
When have I ever been able
to convince Cersei of anything?
我什么时候能这么做过
说服瑟曦吗
If not for yourself, if not for her,
如果不是为了你自己，如果不是为了她，
then for every one
of the million people in that city,
然后对于每一个
在那座城市的百万人口中，
innocent or othennise.
不管是无辜的还是邪恶的。
To be honest,
I never really cared much for them.
说实话，
我从来都不怎么在乎他们。
Innocent or othennise.
不管是无辜的还是邪恶的。
You do care for one innocent.
你确实关心一个无辜的人。
I know you do.
我知道你喜欢。
And so does Cersei.
瑟曦也是。
She has a reason now.
她现在有理由了。
The child is the reason
she'll never give an inch.
孩子就是原因
她决不会让步的。
All the worst things she's ever done,
she's done for her children.
她做过的所有坏事，
她受够了她的孩子们。
It's not impossible that she'll win.
她获胜并非不可能。
She won't.
她不会。
Her enemy's forces have been depleted,
as she said they would be.
她的敌人的力量已经耗尽，
就像她说的那样。
Two of the three dragons are dead.
三条龙中有两条死了。
- She's evened the odds.
- The city will fall tomorrow.
-她扳平了比分。
-明天这座城市就会沦陷。
She has the Lannister army,
the golden company...
她有兰尼斯特的军队
黄金公司……
I defended the city
last time it was attacked.
我捍卫了这座城市
上次它被袭击了。
I know it better than anyone.
It will fall tomorrow.
我比任何人都了解。
明天会下雨。
Then I suppose I'll die tomorrow,
if not before.
那么我想我明天就会死去，
如果以前没有的话。
Escape.
逃跑。
The two of you, together.
你们两个，在一起。
Remember where we met,
记得我们相遇的地方吗？
where they keep the dragon skulls,
beneath the red keep?
他们把龙骨藏在那里
在红堡下面？
Take her down there.
带她下去。
Keep following the stainnays down,
down as far as they'll go.
继续追踪染色，
尽量往下走。
You'll come out onto a beach
at the foot of the keep.
你会来到海滩上
在城堡脚下。
A dinghy will be waiting for you.
有一只小艇在等你。
Sail out of the bay.
驶出海湾。
If the winds are kind,
you'll make it to pentos.
如果风是仁慈的，
你会到达潘托斯的。
Start a new life.
开始新的生活。
Sail right past the iron fleet
and into a new life?
从铁舰队旁边驶过
然后开始新的生活？
Sounds a lot less likely
than Cersei winning this war.
听起来不太可能
比瑟曦赢得这场战争更重要
There won't be an iron fleet
for much longer.
不会有铁舰队
会持续更长时间。
Do it.
这样做。
If you don't,
you'll never see Cersei again.
如果你不知道，
你再也见不到瑟曦了。
Swear to me.
向我发誓。
You have my word.
我向你保证。
If it works,
如果成功了，
give the order to ring all the bells
in king's landing and open the gates.
下令把所有的钟都敲响
在君临打开城门
That will be our signal
that the city has surrendered.
那就是我们的信号
这座城市投降了。
I never thought
I'd get to repay the favor.
我从没想过
我会报答你的。
Remember, ring the bells
and open the gates.
记住，敲钟
打开大门。
Your queen will execute you for this.
你的女王会因此处决你的。
If Daenerys can make it to the throne
如果丹妮莉丝能登上王位
without wading through
a river of blood,
不用费力
血流成河
maybe she'll show mercy
to the person who made that possible.
也许她会发发慈悲
感谢让这一切成为可能的人。
Tens of thousands of innocent lives...
成千上万无辜的生命……
One not particularly innocent dwarf...
一个不是特别无辜的侏儒……
It seems like a fair trade.
这似乎是个公平的交易。
If it weren't for you,
如果不是你
I never would've survived
my childhood.
我就活不下去了
我的童年。
You would have.
你会的。
You were the only one
你是唯一一个
who didn't treat me like a monster.
没有把我当成怪物的人。
You were all I had.
你是我的一切。
Soldier 1: Eyes on the horizon!
士兵1：看着地平线！
Soldier 2: Load the scorpion!
士兵2：给蝎子装子弹！
Soldier 3: Archers, close up!
士兵3：弓箭手，靠近！
Soldier 4: Up to the espringal!
士兵4：到弹簧那儿去！
Soldier 5: To the back of it!
士兵5：到后面去！
Soldier 6: Archers, line up!
士兵6：弓箭手，列队！
Woman: This way! Come on!
女：这边走！来吧!
Soldier 1: Clear the streets now!
士兵1：马上清理街道！
- Woman: No!
- In, now.
-女：不！
-进去，现在。
- And you, come on.
- Soldier 2: Inside, now!
-还有你，来吧。
-士兵2：快进去！
Man 1: Quickly.
男士1：快点。
Yes. Follow down there.
They're here. Get to the red keep.
是。往下看。
他们在这里。快去红堡。
Father: My son!
Soldier 1: Get inside!
父亲：我的儿子！
士兵1：进去！
Man 2: Just ahead of you,
I can see it!
男士2：就在你前面，
我看到了！
Soldier 1: All right, move it!
士兵1：好了，快走！
Woman: Come on!
Soldier 2: Keep moving!
女：别这样！
士兵2：继续前进！
Soldier 3: Keep going!
Soldier 2: Keep moving!
士兵3：继续走！
士兵2：继续前进！
Soldier 3: Quickly!
Soldier 2: All the way!
士兵3：快点！
士兵2：一路！
Man 3: Come on! Man 4: Come on!
男3：来吧！男4：来吧！
Soldier 4: Keep moving!
士兵4：继续前进！
Soldier 5: Make way
for the golden company!
士兵5：让开
为了黄金公司！
Soldier 6: Close the gate!
士兵6：把门关上！
If you hear the bells ring,
they've surrendered.
如果你听到钟声响起，
他们已经投降了。
Call off your men.
把你的人叫来。
Soldier: Move along now, lads.
士兵：走吧，伙计们。
Soldier 1: That's it.
Soldier 2: Go on, move it.
士兵1：就是这样。
士兵2：快点，快点。
Come on, move, move. Faster, faster.
Come on, move it.
快点，走，走。快,快。
快点，快点。
- Keep going.
- Soldier 2: Keep moving.
-继续。
-士兵2：继续前进。
- Move.
- Soldier 1: Stay with him.
——移动。
-士兵1：跟着他。
Man: Hold on.
Woman: Hold my hand.
男：等一下。
抓住我的手。
Nora: Get behind her.
诺拉：到她后面去。
Soldier 3: Close the gate!
士兵3：把门关上！
- No.
- No, mommy.
——没有。
-不，妈妈。
- Girl: -Let me in! Please!
- No, please, sir!
-让我进去！拜托!
-不，先生！
Man 1: Open the gate!
Soldier 1: Close the gate!
男士1：打开大门！
士兵1：把门关上！
Man 2: Open it!
Man 3: Open the gate!
男士2：打开它！
男士3：打开大门！
- Soldier 2: Get back.
- Look, go over there. Go. Go.
士兵2：退后。
-看，到那边去。走了。走了。
Soldier 3: The gates are locked now!
士兵3：大门已经锁上了！
Woman: Open! Open the gate!
女:开放!打开大门！
Jaime: Soldier! Soldier!
杰米:士兵!士兵!
- Man 4: Please open the gate!
- Go back to your homes!
-男士4：请打开大门！
-回家去！
Stay back! It's closed!
退后!它是封闭的!
Soldier!
士兵!
Soldier 1: Move away! Stop!
士兵1：走开！停!
Man 5: Let us in!
男5：让我们进去！
Man 6: We're not leaving!
男6：我们不走！
Turn!
转!
- Turn it around!
- Soldier: Turn it around!
-转过来！
把它转过来！
Euron: Get back! Back!
攸伦：退后！回来了!
Fire!
火!
Soldier 1: Ready!
士兵1：准备！
Move!
动!
Fire!
火!
- Reload!
- Soldier 2: Reload!
——重新加载!
-士兵2：重新装填！
Faster!
快!
Hurry!
快点!
Fire!
火!
Man 1: Go!
男1：加油！
Man 2: Run!
男人2：快跑！
Qyburn: Your grace.
奎伯恩：陛下。
All we need is one good shot.
我们只需要一枪命中。
The scorpions have
all been destroyed, your grace.
蝎子有
都毁了，陛下。
The iron fleet hold Blackwater bay.
铁舰队守在黑水湾。
Euron killed one of her dragons.
攸伦杀了她的一条龙。
He can kill another.
他可以再杀一个。
Qyburn: Your grace,
the iron fleet is burning.
奎伯恩：陛下，
铁舰队在燃烧。
The gates have been breached.
大门已被攻破。
The golden company...
黄金公司……
Our men will fight harder
than sellswords ever could.
我们的人会更努力地战斗
佣兵做不到。
They will defend their queen
to the last man.
他们会保护他们的女王
敬最后一个人。
Qyburn: Yes, your grace.
奎伯恩：是的，陛下。
The red keep has never fallen.
红堡从未陷落。
It won't fail today.
它今天不会失败。
Man: No, no!
男：不，不！
Jon: Move, move!
乔恩：快走，快走！
Man: Run.
男:运行。
Run!
快跑!
Come on!
来吧!
Soldier 1: Ring the bells!
Soldier 2: Ring the bells!
士兵1：敲钟！
士兵2：敲钟！
Man 1: The bells!
男1：铃铛！
Man 2: Ring the bells!
Woman: Ring the bells!
男士2：敲钟！
女：敲钟！
Man 3: Ring the bloody bells!
男人3：敲该死的钟！
Man 2: Ring the bells!
Woman: Ring the bells!
男士2：敲钟！
女：敲钟！
- Tell the queen to ring the bells.
- Man 4: Ring the bells!
-让王后去敲钟。
-男人4：敲钟！
Ring the bell!
摇铃！
Woman: This way.
女：这边走。
Soldier: Ring the bell!
士兵：摇铃！
Man 1: Ring the bell!
男士1：摇铃！
Man 2: Ring them!
男士2：给他们打电话！
Woman 1: Ring the bells!
女1：敲钟！
Man 3: Ring the bells!
男士3：敲钟！
Man 4: Ring the bells!
Man 5: Help us!
男士4：敲钟！
男士5：帮帮我们！
Man 6: In the name of the...
男6：以……的名义……
Man 7: Ring the bells!
Man 8: Now! Come on!
男士7：敲钟！
男8：现在！来吧!
Man 9: Hurry up!
男9：快点！
Woman 2: Ring the bells!
女2：敲钟！
Get back!
回来!
Stay! Stay!
保持!保持!
Quickly. Quickly.
很快。很快。
Stop!
停!
- Come here!
- Woman: Get off him!
-过来！
放开他！
- Get off me! Get off, bitch!
- No, get off! Help! Help!
-放开我！滚开，婊子！
-不，走开！的帮助!的帮助!
Find somewhere to hide.
找个地方躲起来。
Euron: The kingslayer.
攸伦：弑君者。
Jaime: We need to get the queen
out of king's landing.
詹姆：我们得去找王后
离开君临。
Euron: Listen.
Euron:听。
That's the sound of a city dying.
那是一座城市垂死的声音。
It's over.
这是结束了。
Well, maybe for you.
也许对你来说是这样。
If you kill another king
before you die...
如果你再杀一个国王
在你死之前……
They'll sing about you forever.
他们会永远歌颂你。
You're no king.
你不是国王。
Oh, but I am.
哦，但我是。
And I fucked the queen.
我操了王后。
If iwin...
如果iwin……
I'll bring your head to Cersei
so you can kiss her one last time.
我会把你的头交给瑟曦
好让你最后亲她一下。
Your grace, it isn't safe here
any longer.
陛下，这里不安全
任何更长的时间。
The red keep is the safest place
in the city.
红堡是最安全的地方
在城里。
The unsullied have breached
the gates of the red keep.
无垢者已经突破
红堡的大门。
Maegor's holdfast would be
a better place to wait out the storm.
梅葛的庄园
一个等待暴风雨过去的好地方。
You fought well...
你打得很好……
For a cripple.
对于一个跛子来说。
Another king for you.
另一个国王给你。
But I got you!
但我抓到你了！
I got you!
我抓到你了！
I'm the man
who killed Jaime Lannister.
我就是那个男人
是他杀了詹姆·兰尼斯特
Go home, girl.
回家吧，姑娘。
The fire will get her,
or one of the Dothraki.
大火会把她吞噬，
或者多斯拉克人。
Or maybe that dragon will eat her.
或者那条龙会吃掉她。
It doesn't matter. She's dead.
没关系。她死了。
And you'll be dead too
if you don't get out of here.
你也会死的
如果你不离开这里。
I'm going to kill her.
我要杀了她。
You think you wanted revenge
a long time?
你以为你想报仇
很长一段时间？
I've been after it all my life.
我一生都在追寻它。
It's all I care about.
这是我唯一关心的。
And look at me. Look at me!
看看我。看着我！
You wanna be like me?
你想像我一样吗？
You come with me, you die here.
你跟我来，就死在这里。
Sandor
桑德尔
Thank you.
谢谢你！
Your grace.
你的恩典。
Hello, big brother.
你好，大哥。
Ser Gregor, stay by my side.
格雷果爵士，留在我身边。
Ser Gregor, I command you.
格雷果爵士，我命令你。
Obey your queen, ser Gregor.
格雷果爵士，你得服从王后。
Yeah, that's you.
对，就是你。
That's what you've always been.
你一直都是这样。
You're hurt.
你受伤。
It doesn't matter.
没关系。
You're bleeding.
你在流血。
Man: Alanna!
男:阿兰娜!
Alanna! Have you seen my wife?
阿兰娜!你看到我妻子了吗？
Have you seen my wife?
你看到我妻子了吗？
- Arya: Let go.
- Have you seen my wife?
放手。
-你看到我妻子了吗？
Man: Out of the way!
男：让开！
Man: No!
男:不!
Nora: Take my hand.
诺拉：抓住我的手。
Take my hand.
抓住我的手。
Get up. Get up.
起床了。起床了。
- Nora: No. No.
- Wait! Wait!
-不。否。
——等等!等等!
Fucking die!
他妈的死!
We need to fall back!
我们需要撤退！
Fall back behind the wall!
退到墙后面去！
- Fall back!
- Soldier: Fall back!
-后退！
后退！
Jon: Get out of the city!
乔恩：离开这个城市！
Fall back!
撤退!
- Fall back!
- Soldier: Fall back!
-后退！
后退！
You can't stay here.
你不能待在这里。
You have to keep moving.
你必须继续前进。
We can't go out there.
我们不能出去。
You have to.
你必须这么做。
Everyone out there is dead.
外面的人都死了。
If you stay here, you'll die.
如果你留在这里，你会死的。
Follow me.
跟我来。
Follow me!
跟我来!
Man 1: Come on, quickly. Come to me.
Man 2: It's safer up there.
男1：快点，快点。到我这儿来。
男2：上面更安全。
Man 1: Come on, quickly. All of you.
男1：快点，快点。你们所有人。
Run!
快跑!
Girl: Mama!
女孩:妈妈!
Mama!
妈妈!
Mama! No.
妈妈!否。
Mama! Mama!
妈妈!妈妈!
Mama!
妈妈!
Get up.
起床了。
Get up!
起来!
We have to keep moving.
我们必须继续前进。
Take her.
带她。
Take her!
带她!
- Take her.
- Come on!
-带上她。
-拜托！
Come on!
来吧!
This way.
这种方式。
Cersei: I want our baby to live.
瑟曦：我要我们的孩子活下来。
I want our baby to live.
我想让我们的孩子活下来。
Don't let me die, Jaime.
别让我死，詹姆。
- Please don't let me die.
- It's all right.
-请不要让我死。
-没事的。
- Please don't let me die.
- It's all right.
-请不要让我死。
-没事的。
I don't want to die.
我不想死。
Just look... look at me.
看看……看着我。
- Look at me.
- Not like this.
-看着我。
-不是这样的。
- Not like this. Not like this.
- Look... look... look me in the eye.
-不是这样的。不是这样的。
-看…看起来……看着我的眼睛。
Don't look away. Don't look...
不要看别处。不要看……
Look at me! Just look at me.
看着我！看着我。
Nothing else matters.
其他的都不重要。
Only us.
只有我们。